var otterContent = [
  {
    question: 'How many species of otter exist?',
    answers: {
      right: '13',
      wrong: ['5', '22', '8']
    },
    explain: 'There are 13 species of Otter. Most are endangered, but the North American River Otter seems to be thriving.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which ancient religion considered otters to be nearly sacred creatures and had strict rules about killing them?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Zoroastrians',
      wrong: ['Xenophanes', 'Mesopotamians', 'Sumerians']
    },
    explain: 'The answer is the Zoroastrians. They considered otters to be the dogs of the river or sea and had very strict rules about killing these almost sacred animals. They would also hold ceremonies for otters found dead in the wild.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Surprisingly, Otter moms are totally game for which activity below?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Adoption',
      wrong: ['Singing', 'Coloring', 'Cliff-jumping']
    },
    explain: 'It\'s Adoption! The Monterey Bay Aquarium has discovered that adult female otters will actually raise rescued Otter pups until they are ready to be released back into the wild.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Otters can have up to _____ hairs per square inch.',
    answers: {
      right: '1 million',
      wrong: ['1,000', '100', '100,000']
    },
    explain: 'Can you believe that Otters can have up to 1 million hairs per square inch? They have the thickest fur of any mammal in the animal kingdom.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a tool frequently used by Otters?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Rocks',
      wrong: ['Shells', 'Sticks', 'Hammers']
    },
    explain: 'Otters are big on tools, and will often use rocks to help crack into dinner. While they hunt for food underwater, they’ll even store a rock in the skin under their arms for later use.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Giant Otters are super chatty. How many distinct noises do you think they can make?',
    answers: {
      right: '22',
      wrong: ['9', '46', '15']
    },
    explain: 'Scientists recently concluded a study of giant otters and found that the river-dwellers have 22 distinct noises they make for different situations. On top of that, pups have 11 of their own calls that they intersperse with “infant babbling.” '
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a word for a group of Otters?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Romp',
      wrong: ['Gaggle', 'Swath', 'Tribe']
    },
    explain: 'Otter groups go by a few different monikers, all of which are fairly unique to that crew. Generally, a group of otters on land will go by a romp, while a group hanging in the water is called a raft.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can you guess which playground feature Otters will build for themselves?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Slides',
      wrong: ['Swings', 'Sandbox', 'Rope']
    },
    explain: 'Otter families are usually limited to pups and their mothers, and that duo will spend most of their time either feeding or sleeping. In the downtime, though, otters love to play and will often build themselves slides along the banks of rivers.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a food that Otters eat?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Sharks',
      wrong: ['Urchins', 'Crab', 'Snails']
    },
    explain: 'Deep-diving otters dine on abalone, urchins and Dungeness crab; medium divers subsist on clams, worms and smaller shellfish; and those that stay in shallower waters feed on black snails.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these does NOT have Otters?',
    answers: {
      right: 'Australia',
      wrong: ['Africa', 'Europe', 'South America' ]
    },
    explain: 'Otters are found on every single continent in the world except for Australia and Antarctica. They enjoy the freshwater but they are also known to live in the saltwater of the oceans as well.'
  }
]
